prikid.eu 2018-06-29

# Privacy and Refund Policy

**Privacy policy**

Hi! This is our privacy policy and, if you landed here, it means that you want to learn how we

process your personal data at PRIKID.EU and how we protect your privacy. We won’t let you down!

**Essential information we collect**

In operating our store, it is essential for us to capture some information about your device, such as

your IP address and information related to your visit when you browse our store. For example, this

might include time-stamp, the last page or product you visited, the indication that you logged in.

We do that in order to:

  * remember who you are after you log in so that you do not need to authenticate at each

click;

  * monitor if our website is running with the high performance we are dedicated to
  * providing;
  * let you browse between products without having to start back from the home page at

each click;

  * remember if you put something in your shopping cart before you decide to checkout; and
  * control that your data is processed securely.

We call the information mentioned above “essential information” and we collect it through the

use of cookies. Cookies are small text files that most websites uses. A website places cookies in the

web browser and then reads the information collected through the cookies every time the user

performs an action. We use cookies. Without enabling this mechanism and this kind of cookies

(first-party cookies), we could not provide you with the smooth experience that you expect while

you are navigating.

**Order information you expressly provide**

If you buy something from our store, we will need more specific information about you. To fully

process your order and ship the merchandise you selected, we need your personal data such as

your first and last name, your email address and your shipping and billing address. We also use

your contact and order information to send you communication related to the processing of your

order. We will ask you to provide this information in our “checkout page” before letting you

finalize your purchase with the payment.

**Accounts**

You can sign up for an account if you’d like. This will make us happy because it confirms your

interest in our store. It should also make you happy because we will remember your information

and, when you decide to buy our products, you do not have to provide all of your information over

again -- you just have to log-in. Before registering your account, we will ask you to expressly

provide your consent to this privacy policy. Only if you give us your consent, we will open your

account. We also you the possibility to easily withdraw your consent and delete your account. Just

connect with us at the contact details at the bottom of the page.

**Partial Purchases**

If you have started to buy one of our products, but have not completed the purchase, you may

have provided partial information, such as your email. In that case, we might send you an email to

remind you about your interest. If you are not comfortable in receiving further emails of this kind,

we will give you a simple opportunity to opt-out. Your privacy means a lot to us and we will stop

sending you these communications right away.

**Reviews**

If you have completed a purchase, we will send you an email to ask you to review the product you

bought. We want to be sure that whether you love your purchase or have a complaint, you can

share your opinion with other customers.

**Personalization**

We also use some specific information related to your visit, such as the timestamp of your visit, the

page or the product you viewed, where you are coming from (if you came to our store because you

clicked on an advertisement or you just opened our direct link). This is very similar to the

“essential information,” but we use it to provide you with a personalized experience. The

information on your visit provides us with insights on your interests and allows us to send you

relevant communications. We capture this information through cookies, called a "beacon," that

we allow you to block.

**How do we process your information?**

We use an external provider to run our store, BigCommerce . BigCommerce is based in the US and

is a participant in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and committed to providing best-in-class

service and data protection. You can check its participation in the Privacy Shield here on the

official site of The International Trade Administration (ITA), U.S. Department of Commerce.

Through BigCommerce, we also use other, highly specialized external providers to provide the

most competitive services. For example: Mailchimp, PayPal, Stripe.

  * **Payment:** Our store is PCI-DSS compliant (a very strict industry standard with

requirements for the security of credit card information), but we want to use accredited

companies to process your credit card information. So all payments we provide through PayPal and Stripe.

  * **Shipping:** We integrate with a number of shipping companies to fulfill your orders.

The most commonly used delivery providers we use are USPS, UPS and Ukrposhta.

Partnering with highly specialized external companies allows us to focus on what we do best:

selling great products.

**How can you control your personal data?**

If you are one of our customers who is in the EU, and we are specifically selling our products to the

Member State where you are located, you have specific rights that we are honored to enforce

without undue delay: Access, Correct, Erasure, Port, Object. If you cannot exercise your choice on

your account page or if you do not have an account with us, please reach out to us, at the contact

details at the bottom of this page. We will be more than happy to help.

**How long do we keep your data?**

We keep your data for as long as you have an account with us. We also keep some data for security

investigation. Most importantly, we have specific obligations for fraud detection and tax reasons.

Therefore, we might need to retain certain data even if you ask to delete it.

**Do we have any legal obligations when handling your data?**

Many. We might need to share your personal information to comply with applicable legal

obligations.

**Who can you reach out to for privacy matters?**

You can contact our Data Protection Officer by email:

privacy@prikid.eu

**Do you need to lodge a complaint?**

If you have any privacy complaint, you have the right to lodge a complaint with our supervisory

authority.

**Any update?**

If we update our Privacy Policy to reflect a change or improvement of our services or a new legal

obligation, we will publish the new version on our website, and we will make it clear on our home

page [https://prikid.eu](https://prikid.eu/) so it will be visible as you enter our store.

**Refund Policy**

If you are not 100% satisfied with your purchase, you can either return your order for a full refund or exchange it for something else. You can return or exchange your purchase for up to 30 days from the purchase date. Returned or exchanged products must be in the condition you received them and in the original box and/or packaging.
